Daria in 'Is It College Yet?' is a animation, comedy,
tv movie film directed by Karen Disher.
All vile things must come to an end, and for Daria Morgendorffer that
means it's time to look beyond high school to college.
Our little girl has grown up so fast.
It's time for higher learning, lowered
expectations, and a heavy dose of sarcasm.
Life can't suck more after high school, can it?
Daria Morgendorffer (voice), played by Tracy Grandstaff.
Jane Lane / Helen Morgendorffer / Quinn
Morgendorffer (voice), played by Wendy Hoopes.
Jake Morgendorffer (voice), played by Julián Rebolledo.
Trent Lane (voice), played by Alvaro J. Gonzalez.
Anthony DiMartino / Timothy O'Neill / Kevin Thompson /
Jamie White (voice), played by Marc Thompson.
Tom Sloane (voice), played by Russell Hankin.
Is It College Yet?
is a 2002 American animated comedy-drama television film written by Glenn
Eichler and Peggy Nicoll, and directed by Karen Disher.
The film was the second film-length installment of MTV's animated series Daria, after 2000's Is it Fall Yet?, and
served as the series finale, chronicling the end of high school as the characters prepare for college.
Is It College Yet?
was produced in lieu of an abbreviated,
six-episode sixth season requested by MTV.
Series co-creator Glenn Eichler planned to wrap the show with the fifth-season
finale "Boxing Daria", believing that there was no more story to tell.
The film was first broadcast by MTV on January 21, 2002, released on both VHS and DVD formats on August 27,
2002, and was included on the DVD release of Daria: The Complete Animated Series on May 11, 2010.
The film has yet to see a Blu-ray release.
The film explores themes of high school, college,
graduation, misanthrophy, high school graduation.
The tone is lighthearted.